&gt；&gt；steve kinney：让我们谈谈这个，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So let's talk about that,
谈论这个叫做排版线程的东西。
talk about this thing called
the compositor thread.
过度简化是说浏览器有三个线程。
An oversimplification is to say
that a browser has three threads.
那已经不是真的了
That's not really true anymore,
有些浏览器有其他各种各样的东西，比如特殊的线程。
some browsers have all sorts
of other like special threads.
但是让我们简单一点，假设有三个。
But let's oversimplify for
a second and say that there's three.
UI线程不关我们的事。
The UI thread is none of our business.
UI线程，你就像，我写UI。
The UI thread, you're like, I write UIs.
这更像是Chrome的UI。
This is more Chrome's UI.
这就像标签栏和位置栏以及所有类似的东西。
This is like the tab bar and the location
bar and all of that kind of stuff.
这就是Chrome本身。
That is Chrome itself.
你不能碰那个。
You don't touch that.
你不能接触到它。
You don't have access to it.
那是存在的。
That exists.
渲染器线程是我们大部分时间居住的地方。
The renderer thread is where
we live most of the time.
那是我们的Javascript运行的地方，也是我们绘画发生的地方，
That's where our Javascript runs,
that's where our painting happens,
那里就是布局颠覆发生的地方，对吗？
that's where layout thrashing happens,
right?
我们在那里做的所有有趣的事情。
All of the fun stuff that we do in there.
这就是所有HTML有时会被解析的地方
That's where all the HTML
gets parsed sometimess and
像那样的东西。
stuff along those like there.
Chrome或Firefox、Safari中的每个标签都有这些线程之一。
Every tab in Chrome or Firefox,
Safari has one of these threads.
过去他们都共享一个，这意味着一个网页将会
It used to be that they all shared one,
which meant one webpage would take
放下所有的标签，现在，一个网页只能取下自己的标签。
down all the tabs, now, one webpage
can only take down its own tab.
我们生活在更好的时代。
We live in better times.
所以每个页面都有一个这样的页面，这就是我们所有JavaScript运行的地方。
So there's one of these per page, and
it's where all of our JavaScript runs.
我们所做的一切，几乎所有的事情都发生在那里。
Everything we're doing,
almost everything happens there.
然后我们还有另一个叫做合成器线程的东西。
Then we have this other thing
called the compositor thread.
它唯一的工作就是绘制位图，获取位图，然后将它们发送到GPU，
Its sole job is to draw bitmaps,
take the bitmaps, send them to GPU,
把它们放在屏幕上。
put them on the screen.
所以请记住，绘画制作了一堆位图。
So remember,
painting makes a bunch of bitmaps.
排字员的工作就是把这些东西扔到屏幕上，所以
The compositor's job is to take those and
toss them onto the screen, so
我们把它们交出来，一会儿再谈。
we hand them over, we'll talk
a little bit about it in a second.
因此，当我们绘制时，我们创建位图。
So when we paint, we create the bitmaps.
绘制后，与合成器线程共享位图，
After painting, the bitmaps are shared
with the compositor thread,
有一行共享内存空间使用了一些OpenGL。
there is a line of shared memory
space that uses some OpenGL.
我现在的手波浪，但它是好的手波浪。
I am now getting hand wavy,
but it's fine hand wavy.
以前，它是不可接受的手波浪。
Before, it was unacceptable hand wavy.
这是可以接受的手波浪，因为它是OpenGL。
This is acceptable hand
wavy cuz it's OpenGL.
很酷，所以主线程是CPU密集型的，对吗？
Cool, so
the main thread is CPU intensive, right?
你今天看到我多次固定CPU了，对吧？
You saw me peg the CPU at
multiple times today, right?
当我们阻止它时，什么都不会发生。
When we block it, nothing happens.
合成器线程是GPU密集型的，对吗？
The compositor thread is GPU intensive,
right?
我们可以带走的所有东西都有隐藏的一部分
There's, like, a hidden part here
of everything that we can take away
并将其传递给GPU线程。
from that main renderer thread and
pass it over to the GPU thread.
就像主线程一样，渲染器线程有更多的责任。
Like the main thread has, the renderer
thread, has way more responsibilities.
它必须解析一切，计算样式，绘画，布局，JavaScript。
It's got to parse everything, calculate
styles, paint, layout, JavaScript.
任何我们可以卸载到其他线程的东西，就像做GPU一样，
Anything that we can offload to this
other thread that's like doing GPU stuff,
对，我们应该继续做这件事。
right, we should go ahead and do that.
所以，是的，有很多事情要负责。
So, yeah,
there's a lot of stuff responsible for.
所以我们可以说，嘿，GPU处理这个。
So anything we can say,
hey, GPU handle this.
它会让我们更快。
It's going to make us faster.
那我们该怎么做？
So how do we do that?
我们在管理图层。
We're managing layers.
我马上就会讲到那是什么。
I'll get to what that is in a second.
绘画是超级昂贵的，我们应该避免它。
Painting is super expensive,
we should avoid it.